// creating an array to pass the questions with sl numbers and options
let questions = [
    {
        num : 1,
        question : "Raj Gopal ji Maharaj is the form of which deity?",
        answer : "Krishna",
        options : [
            "Shiva",
            "Krishna",
            "Brahma",
            "Hanuman"
        ]
    },
    {
        num : 2,
        question : "'Brahmotsav' is celebrated for how many days in Madanpur?",
        answer : "5-days",
        options : [
                "3-days",
                "4-days",
                "5-days",
                "None of the above",
        ]

    },

    {
        num : 3,
        question : "Madanpur mandir is associated with which mandir of Vrindavan?",
        answer : "Rang ji ka mandir, Vrindavan",
        options : [
                "Radhavallabh ji ka mandir, Vrindavan",
                "Rang ji ka mandir, Vrindavan",
                "Behari ji ka mandir, Vrindavan",
                "None of the above",
        ]

    },

    {
        num : 4,
        question : "Name the railway station of Madanpur?",
        answer : "Kaurara Station",
        options : [
                "Madanpur Station",
                "Shikohabad Jn.",
                "Firozabad Station.",
                "Kaurara Station",
        ]

    },

    {
        num : 5,
        question : "Madanpur is near Which of the following railway zones?",
        answer : "Northern Railway",
        options : [
                "Western Railway",
                "Northern Railway",
                "Central Railway",
                "Eastern Railway",
        ]

    },

    {
        num : 6,
        question : "Madanpur is located in which district of Uttar Pradesh?",
        answer : "Firozabad",
        options : [
                "Mainpuri",
                "Agra",
                "Firozabad",
                "None of the above",
        ]

    },

    {
        num : 7,
        question : "Which among the following places is nearest to Madanpur ?",
        answer : "Sirsaganj",
        options : [
                "Mainpuri",
                "Sirsaganj",
                "Shikohabad",
                "Agra",
        ]

    },

    {
        num : 8,
        question : "How much is the normal distance/time taken from Agra to Kaurara Rly Stn. (Tilyani-Madanpur) by road?",
        answer : "approx. 78.3km (1hr 20min)",
        options : [
                "approx. 78.3km (1hr 20min)",
                "approx. 100km (2hr 50min)",
                "approx. 50km (1hr 50min)",
                "approx. 120km (3hr 20min)",
        ]

    },

    {
        num : 9,
        question : "Which is the world famous tourist place near Madanpur?",
        answer : "Agra",
        options : [
                "Kanpur",
                "Lucknow",
                "Shikohabad",
                "Agra",
        ]

    },

    {
        num : 10,
        question : "Who presides the pooja paddhati in Madanpur mandir (as per the guidelines of Rangji ka mandir)?",
        answer : "Shri Shri 1008 Swamiji of Rangji mandir",
        options : [
                "Madanpur family",
                "Some mathurs of Madanpur",
                "Shr Shri 1008 Swamiji of Rangji mandir",
                "None of the above",
        ]

    },

]

